Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Fated Team @ Viki
When they're leaving, the two of them...
and when they come back, so that there will be three.
Please help.
- Gun, fighting!
- What is this!!!
- Who are you?
- Jeonju Lee's family's
22nd generation's eldest grandson of the head family and the 9th only son, Lee Gun.
You're just a "post-it girl," just like your nickname.
All I wanted to do was, with all my heart,
I wanted to love someone.
She is my younger sister. Since I lost her when she was very young,
I don't know her face.
When the people who have caused pain are just fine like that,
why are the people who were hurt the only ones who are in so much pain that their heart feels like it's going to explode,
and it feels like we're going to go crazy, exactly why?!
From now on, you are not a post-it
but will become crazy glue.
If they detach you, the jerks' skins will also feel like they are being ripped apart.
We'll show them how great of a person
you are.
Miss Kim Mi Young!
Forget about last night's incident.
Of course, I should.
We aren't going to meet again, anyway.
Episode
It's all going to wrinkle.
Unni!
Again?
People will think you are a parcel delivery employee if you just put on a helmet.
It's on the way anyway.
Then just don't go, or take away that "anyway."
Don't do one of the two, please!
Not everyone can live perfectly.
There should be people like me, too.
What's going on that everyone is all outside, making a fuss?
Like gangsters.
You came, President Lee Gun.
It is an honor that you'll be working with our Daehyung Law Firm.
There is no other reason for changing law firms.
Please handle this case without any disputes.
Yes. Let's go in.
What? What's wrong?
Do you know that man?
No, no.
Here... everyone, Grandmas, Grandpas,
Aunts, Uncles, and all the sisters and brothers...
the enemies of our island have just arrived. Can you see them?
Yeah! Go away!
When those jerks arrive, so that they can't set foot on our island,
let's block them!
That Island keeps causing problems.
I need to go through the reorganization procedure,
because I couldn't even go near the factory. I couldn't even come up with an estimate.
What kind of situation is this?
This is why you need people like us.
Is this the document from that time?
I will look through it.
Miss Kim Mi Young!
The one with sugar, here.
Please drink.
Yes. And about branching out to China.
If you entrust your consultation with our law firm,
we have the right person who'll be perfect.
Well, if you introduce the person to me, I'll look into it.
Ah, come in and sit down.
This person is Jangin Chemical's Ceo Lee Gun.
And this is-
Hello, I'm Min Byung Chun.
I have an appointment, so I'll have to get up soon.
And regarding branching out to China, I'll think a bit more about it.
CEO?
She said she worked at the same company as that trash.
Mi Young, get this done by 12 o'clock.
Yes.
Unni,
give me one of those.
My stomach is killing me.
This damn magic...
*referring to her period
isn't there some sort of magic that can make it come only once a year?
Since the lady he was going to marry ran off to America,
you can't even tell us to wait any longer.
I'm sorry.
An apology is not enough!
Because the lady ran off, and our Jangin stock have dropped by 20% as well,
so everyone is very concerned.
We will bring
Lee Yong.
By Lee Yong, you mean...
You can not do that! The son of a concubine?
The grandson of the head family is still alive!
Even if he is alive, it's something we can't be at ease about.
Are you saying this because you don't know
the fact that all the men in the head family have died in their 30's?
Even though he is the son of a concubine,
a bloodline is bloodline.
If he doesn't get married within this year or if we can't see a descendant by next year,
he will have to give up his place as the grandson of the head family.
Come on in!
Hello, Hyungnim and Grandmother.
I, Lee Yong, greet you for the first time in 22 years.
Please take good care of me from now on.
Mother-in-law, have you been well?
It's been a long time, please accept your daughter-in-law's greetings.
Have you been well, Gun?
You've grown up so much since I last saw you! Did you miss your aunt?
Why are you fussing so much? No one's watching.
Just sit down.
I must be the only one happy to see you.
Since he died, we haven't met even once.
I missed you so much.
I did miss you,
so much that I would spring up in my sleep.
I'm telling you to be sure but it's exactly for a year.
Within that time, if my Gun gets
married and has a descendant,
they will have to leave immediately.
Since children in this family have always been so scarce,
you should quickly get it done and add something to this family.
Of course, even though he is lazy in other ways, he is very diligent in that area.
Give him a position at our Jangin, too.
Even a job?
I didn't even think of that yet.
Thank you.
Self-diagnosing Pregnancy Test
Submit.
It can't be.
It's probably not it. It has to be no.
Why do you keep avoiding me?
I'm not avoiding you.
Why didn't you tell me that the person from the casino is the CEO of Jangin Chemicals?
Do you still keep in touch with him?
We don't keep in touch.
We just happened to be together that night.
Then it was a one-nighter? With your personality?
Want me to find out his number?
Meet him,
and help me out, too.
Jangin is planning on branching out to China this time,
and I might become their in-house lawyer.
Can't you do me a favor? Huh?
I'm not close with him.
He is just a grateful person who helped me.
I usually can't refuse, but I really can't do you this favor.
I'm sorry.
Then you don't have to do something that you'll be sorry for.
Is it hard to do what you already did once? You put up a pretense all this time, acting innocent,
but you already got caught by me that you're lying.
What are you doing? Let me go.
How did you seduce Jangin Chemicals' CEO? It's really fascinating.
What's there to see in a woman who's as average as you?
Do you have some back up? You must be okay with not working at the company?
Can I spread a rumor saying that you did all sorts of things to seduce Jangin Chemical's CEO?!
You know that you're finished at the company if a rumor about a man spreads-
It's me, Gun.
Does it hurt?
Please spread the rumors.
That I'm trying to seduce Miss Kim Mi Young, but no matter
what I do, because she won't fall for it, that I'm about to die.
Trash overseas is also trash here, too.
Even that dirty and indecent spirit is still the same, huh?
I will entrust consultation regarding branching out to China with this law firm.
But under one condition.
This trash...
fire him.
Miss Kim Mi Young.
Hello.
Let's go.
Thanks for saving me back there.
You were living like that all this time?
After I transformed you into a Bond Girl...
Sorry.
But why do you keep touching your belly?
Is that a potbelly?
It's a potbelly, right?
Yes. Yes!
Yes, it's a potbelly.
This is what you call a potbelly. How did you know?
Although my frame is petite, my growth of a
potbelly was particularly different than others.
You're very keen. Potbelly.
Dad!
Stay quiet! Who are you calling, Dad?
Shh! Be quiet.
- Dad!
- Dad?
Dad!
This! This isn't a potbelly?
It's a potbelly.
- It moved! There's a child in here!
- What do you mean it moved? Where?
This is my baby, isn't it? I'm right!
- Then I'm becoming a dad?
- No, it's not your baby.
Mi Young, please have this baby. You have to have it! Really!
- It's Dad, you rascal. Dad!
- Dad!
Please congratulate us! Our Kim Mi Young is having a baby!
Why are you suddenly like that?
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Oh yeah. Are you seeing Se Ra again?
Yes.
Yeah.
That's good. I thought it would be like that.
That's good.
Rock, Paper, Scissors!
Oh, it's Ji Woo!
Do it fast. Or it won't be fun.
One, Two, Three, Four,
Five, Six, Seven, Eight,
Nine...
Ready or not, here I come.
Priest.
Can I confess my sins even if I'm not a believer?
Uh... well, you still sin even though you're not a believer.
I'm not a believer, so
I don't exactly know how to do a confession. Will that be okay?
Uh. Actually,
I don't really know either.
You are an amusing priest.
Instead of doing it right now, it'll be okay to do it later.
Priest, I...
I... I think I'm pregnant.
I think so... Although, I might not be...
I'm pretty sure I am.
To be honest, I'm scared.
I'm afraid of having the baby,
and to think of an abortion,
I feel really sad.
I'm scared that people like my mom, sister, and colleagues will find out.
Does the baby's father know this, too?
No.
It's that...
He already has a girl he loves.
He would just feel distressed if I tell him.
He has been hurt enough
because of sleeping with me.
It's okay for me to have a hard time alone. I don't want to do that to him, too.
Then go and buy a pregnancy test at the pharmacy straight from here.
After you find out if you are pregnant or not,
make sure to discuss it with the baby's father.
Do I really have to discuss it with him?
Of course. He is the baby's father. You have the duty and the right to do so.
Even if it is hard and you don't want to, you have to do it. Okay?
Okay.
There are long, round, plate-shaped, and paper-made pregnancy tests.
Recently, there are electronic ones, too-
Priest, I think you know too well.
Sister, this is common sense.
Thank you Priest, for listening to me.
Hey!
Cheer up!
Bye.
I came here because I heard that you were in the CEO's room.
Don't call me Hyungnim at the company.
Call me CEO, you unmannerly bastard.
Ah... yes, Hyungnim...
CEO.
If you go to the public relations department, they will give
you an assistant manager's desk, so start working today.
An assistant manager?
Why? It's not to your liking?
It's not that.
It's not that, but I'm not very familiar with how the company works yet...
Not very familiar?
Not. You don't know anything!
Yes, I don't know anything.
Just because I'm the CEO's brother, getting special treatment. I don't like that either.
I have never acknowledged you as my younger brother.
So, there won't be any special treatment.
Oh, that's right, a package came for you.
It's Park Kyung Chul from Yeoul Island.
Yeoul Island's President Park.
Assistant Manager Min? Leave now.
Why are you putting your feet on the desk.
We got you.
What is this?!
Jangin Chemical's CEO from Seoul.
Huh? What is this?
And this is Miss Kim!
This lady is...
Even though it's been blurred out, it's not Lady Se Ra...
I don't think it's her... Oh!
Chief Park.
Yes!
What is Lawyer Hong's law firm number?
As soon as I came out of that room, I took out the memory chip.
Isn't it perfect?
Then, you dropping it in the water was fake?
- Hamo Hamo.
- Wow, President Park!
That was the best plan in the world.
- You are better than I thought.
- Hamo Hamo!
Hamo Hamo!
But because your sister-in-law's face was in it, I couldn't even tell anyone.
I, for a whole month, painstakingly erased her face, bit by bit.
Lost all my strength. Lost it.
You've suffered a lot.
What are you freaking doing out here, when the restaurant is empty?
We're comfortable here.
Anyway, this is so delicious that you wouldn't even know if both of you dropped dead while eating, right?
You're right, Mother-in-law. This is really delicious!
It's tasty, right?
Then, eat it deliciously and you can both drop dead.
A customer that should have come isn't even coming...
Did you see? The day my mother-in-law finds out, my sister-in-law is a dead person.
- I don't have a mouth.
- Yes.
Hello.
USB.
Call the CEO's Secretary, hurry.
Hello.
- They are not picking up?
- What do you mean they are not picking up?
CEO? Whew, wait...
I'm the person who ran up from the stairs.
Safe!
Does this make sense?
I even forgave them for doing something so low.
How can he stab someone's back in this manner?
Illegal protest, threats... I'm going to stick all of them in jail!
Feed them beans with rice, receive compensation for damages...
I'm going to stick all of them in! All of them!
But, who is this woman?
I don't really know. It's my first time seeing her.
That's right. That Kim Mi Young took vacation days, so she isn't here.
Why are you telling me? Did I ask?
Ah, yes.
But this woman, did they put her in the room?
I don't know, I don't know!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
If we commission a professional, we can probably undo the woman's face.
To tell you the truth, we can win the trial and put them in prison.
We have grounds for damage compensation.
However, you'll lose more than what you'll gain.
Nowadays, if it goes on the internet and it becomes a hit,
we won't be able to handle the situation.
I can just laugh.
Tyranny of the alpha... don't you think you'll hear that?
Wait. He's the one who's legally at fault. Why should I be the one criticized?
These people have abandoned all reason!
Those people are desperate.
Because their life is on the line, the reason gets lost.
Does this make sense?!
Just do what I say.
If the lawsuit progresses, I'll get an attorney fee, so it'll be good for me.
It's for the sake of Jangin Chemical.
Go to Yeoul Island and meet with the representatives.
Both sides should compromise.
That will benefit you.
Must tell Mother.
Not tell her.
Must tell her.
No, yes, no yes, no... yes, no,
yes, no...yes.
No.
If Mom knows this truth, she's going to break both of my legs.
Mi Young!
It is Mi Young!
I heard you are working in Seoul, but you must have come to see your mom, right?
Yes, I took some vacation days off and came down.
Then, tell your mom to make you lots of delicious foods!
Have fun then go back, okay?!
Yes.
But I should still tell Mom?
Mom!
Where are you looking? Right here, here!
Straight ahead!
Wench, you should have at least told me you were coming.
Should I find out by a phone call from Chang Gyu's mom?
What did you come here for?
Mom... Mom, I...
I...
Are you crying right now?
Why are you crying?
Why? Did something happen?
No, it's just, I'm happy to see you!
Aigoo wench, you're being so particular...
People will think you're crying because you got rejected by a man.
Quickly run over here.
Mom!
Aigoo, aigoo.
Are you happy?
How have you been?
Ah!
How could you eat so well?
You are eating similar to me.
Let's just say I eat well since I'm pregnant.
Wow, you eat well.
Because Mom's food is the best in this world.
You're right. You know I have killer hands for cooking.
Aigoo, if you get it with that hand, then it's just right to die today.
Oh yeah. If you went to Macao, you should brag.
Why are you so quiet?
There are a lot of cool men there, right?
Your sister has been on this island for over 40 years looking at the same men,
my eyes haven't gotten upgraded.
Look, look. My eyes are simmering... simmering out of boredom!
Why are you taking out a year?
You were married and went to live in Seoul for a year.
I would be happy even if I have to see my honey for ten thousand years!
Stop it!
And if you're married, you should stay at your house.
Why are you always here lounging around, eating our food?! What about your husband?
He said that he has to talk with President Park all night due to the problems with the factory.
I'm going to sleep in Unni's room tonight.
Also, Mom! How much do I eat anyway?!
You can't mistreat a pregnant lady like this!
Mom, I'm going to sleep with you in your room tonight.
I have something to tell you, too.
With me?
Aigoo. It's best not to sleep with her if you can.
Boss!
Boss! Are you okay?
Blood! It's bleeding!
- Nose bleed!
*sounds like coffee
- Oh, coffee.
I've put a lot of syrup in it.
You used to drink only black.
Why do you keep asking for sweets lately?
My nose is bleeding! Nose bleed! Give me napkins!
Napkin...
Napkin.
Se Ra
It's Lady Se Ra.
Just bring me some napkins.
Prepare for Act 2.
Se Ra?
Okay. I'll be right there.
Okay.
Oppa, it's me.
Are you still really mad at me?
Are you doing well?
I know you're doing this to punish me.
I'll receive the punishment.
In return, don't be sad by yourself.
Just like you've waited for me, I can wait, too.
But can't I listen to your voice just once?
I'm sorry.
How tired must my mom have been to start snoring right when she lies down?
Mom, I'm really sorry for being a pathetic daughter.
When I've never been someone you can brag about,
I go around causing trouble like this, like a fool.
Mom,
no matter what I say,
don't get too shocked.
Mother of 3 Daughters Restaurant
Unni! What are you doing there and not sleeping?
I'm exercising under the moon.
(Something people laugh at in Korea)
Are you not sleepy either?
Mother of 3 Daughters Restaurant
What did I tell you? You can't sleep with Mom, can you?
Is it that good?
Didn't you just stretch to digest your food?
Since I've digested it, it's now time to eat.
You want a bite?
I'm good. Have it all to yourself.
Watching you eat earlier, you eat just as much as I do.
But how did you know you were pregnant?
Pregnancy test?
But you know, that's not really that accurate.
When I first used it, it said I wasn't pregnant.
Once I did it again, at that time, it came out accurately.
Really?
You have to do it with the first urine of the morning.
That's when the hCG pregnancy hormone is the highest.
So it's the most accurate.
But why do you ask?
My friend asked. Eat some more.
Maybe it's because it's an island.
The morning breeze feels cool.
The air is refreshing, too.
Refreshing? It's frustrating because of the salty smell.
CEO, since you came to negotiate anyways,
Yeoul Island is famous for it's anchovy lettuce wrap, so make sure to add that in when you're negotiating.
It'll be a favorable negotiation.
Am I crazy? I'm already annoyed with having to deal with people, I ought to just stick them in jail right now!
What anchovy lettuce wrap? I'm going to take revenge on them, short and brief. (sounds like lettuce wrap)
I'm going to take revenge!
Lettuce wrap.
Are you okay?
Wench, why are you so surprised between family?
Why does the door open like this?
We have to fix it soon.
Hey, what is that thing your hiding behind you?
What? It's nothing.
Why are you hiding it if it's nothing?
You... It's the same face your sister makes when she is caught eating.
Mom.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
Because you might be too shocked...
What is this?
There are two lines. That means you're pregnant.
What? Pregnant?
- Who?
- Pregnant? Who?
Is that why you asked me about the pregnancy test last night?
It's not your friend, but you, right? It's you who's pregnant, aren't you?
Is what Mi Ja saying true? It's not, right?
I heard wrong, didn't I?
Mom, I was going to tell you right as soon as I came, but-
- Mom.
- You wench!
Mom, stop it!
You're going to hurt her!
Say it. Who is it? The one who made you like this?
I really don't know who it is.
Oh yeah? Then get hit with this until you know.
Mom! I'm sorry.
Did you go to Seoul to recklessly roll your body around like that?
If you don't say it right now, who the baby's dad is,
you're really going to die in my hands!
- He's dead.
- What? He's dead?
Yeah.
No, he couldn't be dead.
If he was, you couldn't have eaten the lettuce wrap so deliciously!
It's positive he's not dead.
Oh, right!
You went to Macau with a man, didn't you?
Mom, that's right! The man she went to Macau with is the culprit!
It's not that man!
It's a man I don't know.
Then, it was a one-night stand?
What stand? Are you talking about that thing you pull to turn on the light?
After turning the "stand", off, you sleep together for one night, the next day, you act like you don't know each other
by saying "When have we met?" As you end with "Bye bye." There's something sad like that.
Aigoo! I can't believe you would be first in doing a one-night stand that I wanted to do so much.
Be quiet.
You! Bring that "stand" bastard right now!
Mom, it's the truth. I don't know who he is.
Oh my...
You slept with him without even knowing who he was?
Actually...
Kneel!
Actually,
I went into the wrong room... unknowingly, well, I...
It's all my fault!
Aigoo... aigoo, this retarded idiot!
You get fooled by some bastard and after sleeping with him,
are you protecting him right now?!
- Imagine how much she fell for him to do this.
- Oh crap. What's happening here?
You idiot, idiot! You put in too much stimulant!
You get up right now! Let's go to Seoul!
Mom! Mom...
That man has a woman he likes.
How can I break up their relationship?
You have a huge advantage!
When you have a baby inside your stomach, what's there to be scared of?
Aigoo! Aigoo, my rotten fate!
There are four women in the household, but three of us don't have a mate!
Why is it so crappy?
Let's all just jump into the ocean and die together!
- Let's go. Let's just die.
- I'm sorry.
- What's the point of living?
- Mom!
Mother-in-law! Mother-in-law! Mother-in-law!
I...
I know... who the baby's dad is.
Yeoul Soap Factory
Here.
First of all, the reason why I came here
is not because I am afraid of the threat.
Even more so, I'm not here to fight these people back
who engage in these illegal behaviors.
He couldn't hold back just a little longer and said he'd come back after seeing his wife...
why is Mr. Choi not coming?
After stopping and thinking about it for a while...
Maybe... reeeaaallllyyyy just maybe, I thought
I have progressed the work too unilaterally, so
I found myself coming this way.
Then let's now move to a different place,
and try to talk frankly in our own perspectives.
That was a great speech.
Talk about the anchovy lettuce wrap… lettuce wrap with anchovies.
Ah, also, I heard that the most famous and delicious dish on this island is
lettuce wrap anchovy!
I like it, too! Lettuce wrap anchovy!
Lettuce wrap anchovy, I really like it!
- Really?
- Yes, I like it.
Wow, how did you know!? In Yeoul Island, it's anchovy lettuce wrap-
No-no-no, it's lettuce wrap anchovy!
Lettuce wrap anchovy!
It's this way, this way!
In our island, we call even the Ahjumma at the restaurant, "Mother."
"Mother, anchovy-" no-no,
"Please give me lettuce wrap anchovy, please!" Then you'll get an enormous amount of food.
Your tongue has to gather up in an "S" shape, and say, "Mo~ther." Try it. "Mo~ther."
- Mother.
- Aigoo! That's awkward. "Mo~ther".
- Mo~ther.
- Aigoo! You're good.
Mo~ther.
- Mo~ther!
- That was good!
Mo~ther! That was good!
Lettuce wrap anchovy!
Lettuce, lettuce, lettuce wrap anchovy!
Mom! Mom!
Are you really not going to follow me?
Do you think I will let that bastard be just because you won't budge from here?
I told you, it's not that person's fault.
- Come here!
- Mom!
We're here. We've arrived.
She's our mother and the restaurant ahjumma!
- Mother, Mother.
- Mother?
Mo~ther!
Please give me a l~ot of lettuce wrap!
Oh, wait, wait.
Kim Mi Young... Kim Mi Young, what are you doing here?
Kim Mi Young...
Why are you here?
Mother-in-law! It's... it's that person!
That... Dding hao, dding hao!
Ah, oh yeah, this is Yeoul Island! Right, right.
What?
Lettuce wrap!? You should be the one wrapped and eaten!
Who are you asking to give you a lettuce wrap!?
Eat this instead!
No, Ahjumma! Why? Why are you hitting me?
I'm doing it to you! Then who else would I do it to?
You were the one who played around with my daughter!
Mom, you can't do this! Don't do this!
Just hit me instead.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
No, no.
Ahjumma, Ahjumma, I don't know what's going on but let's use words... words.
What? After doing something that makes no sense, you want to talk it about?
Are you doing this because you don't know what you've done to my daughter?!
Wait! Wait! Ma'am!
Ma'am, I know about that incident. But
instead of violence, using words-
What? You know?
Are you acting like this even though you know?
This bastard! You should die in crap water!
Ah! Ah! It was by mistake! It was like that. It was a mistake!
Right! Of course, it was a mistake!
Mom, I already told you this person did nothing wrong.
You, because you did the "stand" with my daughter...
Mom, one-night stand!
With my daughter, because you did that "stand",
- My daughter is now-
- Mom!
Please do me a favor. Don't say it. I'll... I'll just take care of it.
This person did nothing wrong.
It all happened because of my mistake.
Whenever I was having a hard time, this person helped, encouraged, and protected me. Mom!
Is this the result of protecting you?
Because of you, my daughter is now pre-
Mom!
I will say it instead. Let me tell him, please?
You say it. Now!
Now.
The thing is... I... your...
You're what? Just say it comfortably. It's okay.
As if this is your house, I'm okay because I can accept it.
So tell me.
- Your...
- "Your" what?
Ah... "your" what? "Your" what?!
I'm pregnant with your child.
What is she saying right now?
Isn't that something good?
It's your child though.
It's my child then, right?
Baby... baby...
My... my...
WHOA!!
I'm sorry. What to do... I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry? You retarded idiot!
This is why I have to step up!
I understand how you feel, but
right now, we're in the middle of negotiations.
The CEO has to be here to keep moving forward.
Wait a second! Wait!
Move.
Mother-in-law,
you know that this situation is really important to the people of our island.
I'm right, aren't I?
Aigoo!
Do you need to be beaten with a stick!
You can negotiate later,
but this matter has your sister-in-law's life on the line!
What kind of brother-in-law are you!? You understand!?
Of course, of course! You're right!
I know we were desperately waiting for a negotiation,
but right now, it seems best if we back out. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
You! Your name is Gun, right?
Yes.
I'm the grandson of the head family... what generation am I?
9th generation.
Yes, it's Gun.
All right, Lee Gun!
We still have a lot to talk about, right?
Yes. That's right. We do have a lot to talk about.
Follow me.
- Mother!
- Ma'am!
What is a one-night stand?
Hurry up and order the food.
Ah, stand...
Can you talk right now?
-Yes, it's okay. Please continue.
As expected, the basic personal data matches up.
As of right now, the probability of this person being your sister is the highest.
You just have to wait for the results of the DNA test.
For how long?
I can't wait till then. I will go there tomorrow.
No, I'll go to Tonghyung and meet her in person.
What is this?
What will this be?
Ah, it won't be good if you get too excited and scream.
What is it?
Tada!
Oh my! What is this?
This is Da Wan's work!
How did you get this?
I spent some money in order to see you this happy.
How could you...
as if you came in and out of my heart!
Oh my world.
How could I not love you?
Aigoo.
Do you like it?
Yes, I love it.
Who is he?
That handsome person I see.
Mom, Mom!
There is a visitor. Even by a glance, his looks are about the same level as mine.
He is tall too. Do you know who he is?
Name: Daniel Pitt
Age: 32
A global designer who's being called the second Philippe Starck in the industry.
Never tells outsiders about coming into Korea, and refrains from public events.
He has revived a dead company with his designs.
He is friends with Mother, overtaking the age difference.
His spec is grand and impressive.
However, he's not someone who should be first on the blacklist yet.
Here, a nuclear weapon that will blow this whole household.
It'll look cool if the hero holds onto it.
Are you sure that you really didn't know?
Huh? You're not making excuses.
I'm not that kind of person.
I've really never made excuses since being born.
I just didn't know that she was pregnant.
Mom, I told you that I didn't tell him.
Why do you keep doing this, putting him in a difficult spot?
Since you've said that you are not going to back out,
shouldn't your family members
know this fact now, right?
Call your family in front of my eyes right now.
You can't.
Why aren't you calling them?
Mom, can't we take care of it on our own?
I think that that will be better.
I don't think so.
Do you think that I don't know you?
You are probably just going to say "I'm sorry, I'm sorry."
You'll say that a hundred times and end it.
You.
Hold on, CEO!
Won't she receive less of a shock if I call first?
I'm sorry.
If I went to the right room, this wouldn't have happened.
It already happened.
Do you think you being like this will do any good?
I have a responsibility, too,
so I will take care of it.
If Chairwoman finds out, she will be shocked.
What is this?
Who are you?
Our island's enemy, CEO of Jangin Chemical.
Hey, what are you doing?
How can this be? This makes no sense.
How can the grandson of our family do this?
How is he going to meet our ancestors?
I just can't watch this.
Who is that girl? I don't think she's Se Ra.
After looking at the thickness of her wrist and ankles, and the condition of her hair,
she seems to be about 160 cm and weighs about 45 kg.
She seems to be a woman with very ordinary looks.
That's amazing. You are the best at this kind of thing.
Turn it off right now!
Grandmother, talking to those two directly first,
seems to be the right order to figure out the truth.
Right?
Giving Gun a call right now is the right thing to do, right?
Where is my cellphone?
Is it Gun? Where are you right now?
Come see your grandmother right now.
Grandmother, it's going to be difficult to go see you right now.
The place I'm at is-
Hello. Is this Gun's grandmother?
I am Kim Mi Young's mother.
Who is that?
Kim Mi Young,
is the name of my valuable daughter whom your grandson impregnated.
What?
Did you just say "pregnant?"
Yes. There is no denying it. She is pregnant.
How can this happen?
So the baby inside of your daughter's stomach
is the baby or my grandson for sure?
Did you just say "for sure?"
Are you saying I'd do this with my daughter when I'm not sure?
What? Are you planning to back out?
What do you mean "back out"?
Our household's specialty is taking responsibility.
I will go there right now.
But where is that?
Yeoul Island. You can take a boat to get here.
Mom, there probably won't be anymore boats coming in today.
Oh my. Today won't do.
The boat comes here two times a day,
but the last boat just left.
I will tightly hold on to your grandson and my daughter so they can't run away,
so as soon as the day brightens, you can come here.
As soon as the sun rises,
I will no matter what, no matter what runs over there...
So please, I ask you to take care of my grandson so nothing happens to him.
Aigoo, of course!
Do you perhaps think
I'd do something to your grandson?
Aigoo!
Why are you like this, Grandmother? What happened?
She's pregnant.
Pregnant?
This pregnant?
This rascal!
After doing this, how can he not tell me?
Daniel! Daniel!
My Gun, my Gun...
He is letting me see my great-grandchild, which I have been waiting for.
What are you doing? Follow me.
Chief Park!
Here, you two can sleep here.
No way! No way!
How can we sleep together? And in this kind of place at that.
No, no.
Mom, we have Unni's room and your room.
I can sleep here,
but he is a guest, after all.
Yes, I'm a guest.
Aigoo, guest, my ass.
You are a thief who stole the soap factory and my daughter.
Go in already.
No, I can't.
How can I sleep here? It is smelly and dirty.
Where? It smells fresh.
It's homey and nice.
Ow!
- Come in.
- I can't sleep here!
I can't sleep here!
What is happening?
What is this sound?
She locked the door!
Why is she locking the door? Are we prisoners?
Open the door!
Open!
Ahjumma, just hit me like earlier instead.
Please open the door!
Fated to Love You
~ Preview ~
I think that we should go to the hospital tomorrow.
I made a selfish decision, but I hope that you'd follow me.
You are asking to give my Mi Young as a surrogate, aren't you?
How dare you act like a rude chaebol?
You need to be in love to marry.
You cruel rascal!
They're all the same.
So will you pray with me?
If we met under nice circumstances,
I'm sure we would call this "fate".
I got married.
I got married!