Subtitles Brought To You By The Fated Team @ Viki
- What is this?
- Cut.
Unni, why?
Episode
Hyeri, what's the matter?
Where is Manager Do?
Oh Noona, I'm here.
What is wrong?
Can you say things like that after looking at this situation?
Try to do something!
Miss Hyeri, if you have something to say, you can tell me. What's wrong?
When all the other places use a stand-in,
it doesn't make sense for me to be only one doing this!
Well, you already signed the contract.
For the model to do it personally, without using a stand-in.
Anyway, this is too much! I don't think this is right.
I know that you are really suffering a lot,
but let's just go one more time.
Director, I'm the one who has been picked four years in a row
for having the most desirable hair by the CEOs.
If my hair gets all ruined after using a shampoo like this,
how are you going to take responsibility for it then?
Okay, okay. I got it. Okay, I will do it.
Then go and bring mine.
You know the one from Finland, the one with White Birch extract.
Okay.
Move this!
Let's go.
Wait a moment.
Do you know me?
But who are you to be here...
Oh my, what is this? Who is he?
Hey!
Who are you to be here?
Even if your hair gets wet,
and even if the lights are hot, never be shocked.
As if this is your own house, be natural...
And without hesitation,
the work of 3 generations of artisans,
from ruined hair...
with the determination of letting it get to
he root of your hair...
you have to be thorough, really thorough!
Lastly, with the satisfaction from using the shampoo.
You explode into a big laugh.
The words that comes out without even me knowing,
"I feel fresh."
Cut.
Without even me knowing, it was so perfect...
- What?
- But who are you?
Me?
President! President!
Excuse me...
President, something big has happened!
What...
Something happened here, too.
I'm President Lee Gun from Jangin Chemical.
Attention please, This is not "just a shampoo."
With our Jangin Chemical's name on the line, this is the number one product,
that's been in production for 3 generations which has history and authenticity.
The reason why I wanted a model instead of a stand-in
was because of my wish for the authenticity of this product to be relayed well to the customers.
I'll say again, but this is not "just a shampoo!"
- Director Tak?
- Yes, sir.
Get the penalty fee ready.
No, no president. I can do it.
This time, I think that the director will approve of this cut.
Or while eating dinner together,
we can talk again about the contract.
It's fine.
You, who have no amount of authenticity.
A model like you who just asks for a lot of money.
I don't need you.
Get lost.
Here, keep going.
President!
How many times is this!
Why do you keep doing this?
President, why are you...?
What is the big problem?
Oh. Yeah... There is a big problem, President!
Chairwoman Wang was called by the elders.
Jeonju's Lee Family Emergency Meeting
To my Gun, there is a girl that he dated for six years.
You all know that our Gun, without his sense of responsibility and trustworthiness,
is just an empty corpse.
Please trust him. I'll make sure he gets married this year.
You said 3 years ago that he will get married when he becomes thirty.
Do you think we will get tricked again?
If it is true, you have to sign a contract
saying that Gun will get married in 100 days.
Is all this really necessary?
You can't even give us some assurance?
This is a critical time when our blood line might end.
What is your problem, Chairwoman Wang?
Lee Gun, Jeonju's Lee family's 21st generation grandson and the 9th generation only son.
I greet all the elders here.
I, Lee Gun, working at a company that my grandmother worked to raise in her youth,
I made our Jang In Chemical the number one company in the daily supply field.
Even right now, the company is well know, all around the globe
I made it possible that the stock rose 5 times...
more than 5 times.
Thanks to this, each and every elder here
doesn't have to worry about your retirement fund. I find this to be very worthwhile.
Your yacht and mansions you bought last time; you are managing them well, right?
The woman that I love
is finally coming to Korea.
I will, on my honor and not my grandmother's,
this fall, I will definitely
get married!
Wasn't I cool?
♫ Buy it, use it, break it, fix it, trash it, change it, mail - upgrade it. ♫
♫ Charge it, point it, zoom it, press it, snap it, work it, quick - erase it. ♫
♫ Write it, cut it, paste it, save it, load it, check it, quick - rewrite it. ♫
♫ Plug it, play it, burn it, rip it, drag and drop it, zip - unzip it. ♫
♫ Lock it, fill it, call it, find it, view it, code it, jam - unlock it. ♫
♫ Surf it, scroll it, pause it, click it, cross it, crack it, switch - update it. ♫
Hello.
♫ Scan it, send it, fax - rename it. Touch it, bring it, pay it, watch it, turn it. One more time ♫
Wait for me!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Wait, wait, wait, this is hot!
I'm sorry.
Wait a moment.
Give it to me.
Ah, thank you!
Excuse me.
It smells great.
It is freshly brewed. Do you want one?
Is it okay if I drink it?
It's not the smell of the coffee though...
I think the smell comes from somewhere else.
By the way, why is it that it's always you who does things like this?
Actually, I was on my way out.
- Thank you.
- Have a good day!
Well, I can just eat coffee mix anyway.
Americano made by Chef Joo and a bagel.
Two green cappuccino, Choco cream box
There's always a person like this around.
Not even the part-timer but has to do all the errands.
Already busy with her own work but cannot say no.
Even if they don't thank her, a person who still listens to everyone's requests.
Extra
Coupon.
Kim Mi Young, can you photocopy this?
Kim Mi Young, did you clean the desk yet?
- I need a copy.
- Get me a cup of coffee
Miss Mi Young, go to the court for me.
Miss Mi Young, you didn't water my plant?
Miss Mi Young, photocopy this too.
Miss Mi Young, two glasses of Americano here!
Kim Mi Young, here is today's to-do list.
That's right. I'm Kim Mi Young.
It's a really common and plain name, right? Like my face...
If you look at this post-it, it's like me.
Although it's needed by everyone, no one really thinks it's precious
because it's comfortable and easy to throw away.
- Miss Mi Young, please throw this out.
- Throw this out too.
This too.
As expected, today as well.
Mine too since you're on your way there.
- Oh!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Those particulate-matter-like people...
Unnie, didn't I tell you to stop doing things like this, right?
Every time you do this, it makes me feel upset too.
I have to do it if they asked me.
"I'm not a housekeeper. I'm not doing errands as a part-timer!"
Why can't you say that, Unnie?!
Are you Kim Jung Eun from Lovers In Paris?
I told you to clearly reject them, that you're not doing it.
Why can't I do that? I can't say no.
That's a disease. A disease. You're-too-nice-it's-annoying disease!
It's not because I'm nice.
If I refuse to do it, imagine how embarrassed the other person would be.
I can't stand that.
Even with saying no, it'll work with practice!
Everything is hard at first but it's easier the next time.
From now on, everyday, before you sleep say to your pillow,
No~~! No~~! Practice that.
No~~! No~~!
It's hard.
Will it really work if I practice?
Aigoo.
Miss Mi Young!
Yes, Lawyer Yong.
Here. send this to the court.
Yes, I got it.
Also, can I ask for a favor?
Favor?
I can't do it today.
Okay. I understand. That's possible, right?
Ah, I have to endure it. It'll be fine if the timing goes well.
One second, two seconds, three.
No. As expected, I can't do it.
Sure. I can do a favor. What is it?
It is just a personal errand.
It's okay.
Chores are best when they are personal.
My daughter who's in Canada,
Told me to send these to her.
Cherry pink, Cherry...
Just looking at the name, it's already sweet.
Gun, Gun,
Just now, what you said at the meeting,
Why were you saying it so boldly?
How are you going to manage the aftermath?
Madam Park, this time, Sara has come to South Korea for good.
Welcome to Korea!
- So, for good?
- For good!
- Then, she'll stop doing ballet now?
- She'll stop!
Aigoo! This punk! It's such a good news, why do you only say it now?
It's because I'm happy!
Ahm, just in case,
if she doesn't accept the proposal, what would you do?
What do you mean "just in case"?
Why are you saying something so negative when I'm preparing for a once-in-a-life-time event?!
I'm sorry, President.
Are you sure that I don't have to go with you?
I will pick my lover's ring carefully.
Director Tak, you stay here and prepare the things I told you about without any errors
- Meticulously!
Grandma, I'll get going
- Bye bye!
It must be great. Who could it be?
How about this?
This is the best ring for proposal that we have
This won't do.
It's difficult.
To make it easier for you,
Don't you have omething more elegant and graceful?
Uh, you already looked at all the products we have in our store.
Ah! If you know what kind of person your girlfriend is,
it will make it easier for us to recommend something for her.
She is...
My poet,
not a poem that you read and hear but,
a peon that on the stage, with all her body,
give off a comfortable radiance,
the world is peaceful and wonderful.
Also, it's so still.
Like the days of a young child,
with both arms around me,
like my mother's hug,
she writes poems for me.
She's a special woman like that.
Ah, so cute.
Who is it?
My younger sister. How is she?
- She's pretty, right?
- She's really pretty.
She also takes good care of her brother.
I think the two of you look so much alike.
I also wish it was like that.
I lost her when I was too young, I forgot her face so
I think she looks like this so I drew her as I imagined.
Ah, too obvious and too cheesy.
More than that,
I know for a fact that I won't even recognize her if we meet again.
What should we do?
I'm really sad.
In first grade,
I departed with my sister.
I was in an orphanage and was adopted to America.
Even if I look for him every time I come to Korea.
It's not easy.
This is rotten. Who will fall for that kind of story?
If it was me, I won't fall for it for my pride.
That's right! Yeah, that's right.
Why is this so fun?
Excuse me.
Mouse!
Really...
You heard everything. Be honest if you like me.
Don't act all cute.
Are you being mad because I didn't flirt with you?
What should we do?
You are not my type at all.
- What is your type?
- From head to toe,
Someone who is completely opposite of you will do.
Princess, I welcome you to Magical Candy House.
Princess, if you ever need any help, call us at anytime.
But I'm not a princess...
Princess, those are love love candies that helps you find love.
My oppa gave me this when he confessed to me and it was so sweet,
that I said yes without even knowing it.
I didn't like him that much at the time.
Give me this please.
Princess, you bought a lot.
This is a cherry pink is a gift with purchase.
This is the famous Love Love Candy.
Thank you.
Se Ra,
I think it will suit you well.
I hope you'll accept it.
Oh...
Oh my.
Aigoo aigoo, what should we do...
Ring...
Candy...
Ring!
My ring!
My ring...
My ring, my ring...
Ring... Ring...
Where is it?
There! It's my ring. I said my ring is there!
My ring, my ring!
Go take it, fast!
No, not there but over here.
I'm sorry.
Look over there!
Not there!
Quickly!
Left, Right, Left!!
It's over there!
Oh yeah...
What are you guys doing?
It's over there!
It's going near that dog!
No! That dog rascal!
Go slowly!
What are you doing? The ring...
Pick up that ring!
I really can't touch dogs...
Just go quickly!
I'm scared. Quickly!
He looks scary...
Do it.
Did you get it?
Just a little more.
Almost there!
Did you get it?
A little more?
Did you?
You still can't get it?!
Okay, okay.
Is it the end?
Following my ancestors in my 30s...
Is it the end for you and me?
Father, Grandfather, and the grandfathers after that,
Me too, in the end,
I can't escape fate.
No!
If here's the end, I'll die like a dog.
But,
Who's this woman?
So fast,
She is a fast woman!
No...
Let's go together...
Under construction
What should I do!
No!
What should I do?
Oh my...!
Don't worry,don't worry,
I'll chase him away.
I can do it.
It could be dangerous!
Don't worry.
You rascal. You must be reprimanded.
You rascal. Wait a moment.
I wil-
Don't worry.
You must be reprimanded!
Come here. Come.
That person is weird too. Am I crazy?
Come here!
Is it dead? I killed it, right?
Don't...
Don't touch her!
What should I do...
Hey, you!
Don't touch her!
Just wait. Stay still...
It's this...
Cherry!
Cherry! Why did you follow her?
My goodness.
Oh is this cherry flavored?
He goes crazy if he smells anything cherry.
So that's why his name is Cherry.
Look here,
you should put him on a leash tightly.
What would you have done if it had bitten someone?
I was gonna scold him,
but I held back.
Oh... I'm sorry
He's usually cute and innocent.
I'm sorry. Let's go Cherry, let's go.
Let's go.
My ring! My ring.
Did you get my ring or not?
You didn't get it?
I got it.
I did good right? You're ring is here.
Oww!
Ouch, my finger almost flew off.
What kind of person are you?
Why is this on your finger? This is the ring I'm using to propose!
It's a ring that a different girl isn't supposed to wear!
I was in a hurry and I thought I would lose it.
Also, why did you run and make this situation?
I'm sorry. But isn't it a relief that we found your ring?
Relief? What's a relief?
This precious ring, because of you rolled around,
and then that Cherry or whatever followed you.
There's nothing that was a relief. So why are you saying it was a relief? Why?
How was I supposed to know that the dog followed me because of the candy?
Enough. But if,
if I propose and it turns out bad. Just know that is because you're bad luck. Okay?
Do you know what kind of ring this is? This unlucky situation occured right after I bought it...
This makes no sense. This is unlucky.
- What...
- This unlucky...
This makes no sense!
What kind of person is that? Only saying what he needs to say.
Candy.
Attention please.
Today, as you all know,
It's the 10th anniversary of our giant law firm.
That's why we will start something that the company specially made,
We are going to give out presents.
But I feel like something is missing.
Mi Young isn't here.
Do you have to actually think about that? It's not like you guys are.
Why are you looking after a person that is useless?
Nobody would take notice even if she was absent from work.
That's what I'm saying.
Miss Mi Yong! Thank you.
Leave it there.
In here, is your guys,
name.
The person who is picked,
Will go to the best resort in Macau.
Macau!!
Wow!!
You have to buy your own airplane ticket though.
Why not just give everything?
Whatever. It's fine too.
Whoever it is, is really lucky because I never get picked.
The person who will be taking the fortune is...
Oh I'm nervous.
I'm so nervous.
Kim Mi Young.
It's you.
Which Kim Mi Young?
Ah, there are more than one Kim Mi Young.
Seomul Kim Mi Young.
It's you!
Really me?
Oh my gosh! Thank you!
Congratulations.
Ji Yeon, since this is a couple package you and I can go together.
Do you think I'm crazy to be a couple with you?
Then who do you go with?
It's a problem even when you get picked.
That's why you need a man so that you can use it on cases like this.
No way,
How can I go with you? You have to go with a man to a place like this.
- Meticulously!
- I prepared it meticulously!
The first.
Do you see this?
You got the ring back from the doorstep of death.
The problem is the location of the proposal.
The place that you were planning to use
Is the best resort in Macau,
Thi-... Huh?
That is the place where I first met Se Ra.
That is why you chose this place!
Wow, remembering the first place that you met her,
And proposing.
Is just...
After your parents passed away early on,
How lonely must you have been?
What are you saying right now?
Who are you saying is lonely? I am not lonely!
If I had a younger sibling...
I bet that you are feeling this. For me, you should act like a gentleman.
No, don't act like a gentleman and please,
- Why? Why?
- Surprise!
It's me, Gun!
No!
What's wrong?
Turn on the lights.
You came, Se Ra.
It's good you are here!
Se Ra is here! I said Se Ra is here!
Se Ra is here!
Se Ra! It's been a while since I saw you. You guys can talk privately.
Director?
You came, Se Ra?
Tell me honestly. What did you do without me?
I surrender!
- Tell me.
- Alright! My neck is going to twist.
I was planning.
A plan to go somewhere fun with you.
What is this? You were being good.
Of course.
How did you come here so suddenly?
Didn't you say you were coming tomorrow?
Since it is a surprise like this, aren't you happy to see me?
Are you joking? Of course I'm happy to see you!
It's a shame though...
I was going to do a parade from the airport to here.
With a red carpet made of roses.
Really? Should I leave and come back in?
Don't go.
Now,
I am never going to let you go anywhere again, my love.
Three Daughter's Mother Diner.
Why? Why did you call me?
A trip? You and me together?
What? I want to go too!
Take me with you too, Mi Young! Don't forget about your sister!
Your big sister is bored too. Please let me escape!
You're so loud! Go over there!
Where?
South East Asia?
It's an awfully fine resort! It's in Macau.
Awfully fine resort?
It's okay. You go have fun.
I said I'm not going! Hang up!
Why at a time like this?
Where am I going to go when the whole Island is concerned about the soap factory?
I think I should just sell the tickets.
I feel like the air plane tickets are a waste.
No one wants to go with me.
Won't it be awesome at a time like this to rain men?
So that we could choose according to our liking.
Mi Young!
Hello!
Here is what you ordered! Eat well!
Here, Mi Young.
Aigoo.
Please eat.
- I will-
- No, it's okay.
Let's eat.
How is it?
It's delicious.
I can see you were pressured to say that with that expression.
No! It's really good.
You speak well under pressure.
How did you know?
What do you think of me?
You don't have to answer me now! I don't have to know right away.
- Eat.
- Okay.
Wow!
You look totally different when you're playing music.
As expected.
- Don't fool around and do it like before, okay?
- Yes, Hyungnim.
Hello.
I'm in a meeting at the restaurant in front of the company. Have a good meal.
I'm sending it. Seriously.
Have no fear. Right now.
Send it right now.
What does it say?
It's still on one.
There's nothing yet. I shouldn't have sent it.
He's going to laugh at me, right? He did just buy me a meal...
Wondering why I'm misunderstanding the situation.
No, never.
Males, if they aren't interested in you, they never buy you food.
He read it!
But there's no reply.
I'm going crazy.
Why are you only eating ddukbokki? You should eat rice.
See you later.
- My sweetheart.
- He called you 'sweetheart'!
Unni, it's over. It's over.
He is asking you to date him.
You think so?
You can't just stay still now. You have to go all out.
Tell him you want to go to the resort with him.
- My goodness.
- Just tell him! Send him a heart too!
A heart?
You put it heart there and...
Aigoo.
That person over there, he's really Lawyer Min, right?
Go over there and tell him now. I'm leaving now.
Hey, hey, right now-
Excuse me, Lawyer Min.
Lawyer Min!
LAWYER MIN!
Mi Young.
Was kimbap and ddukbokki delicious?
- Yes.
- That's strange.
I haven't seen you only for a short while, but I already miss you.
Well... about that...
What is it?
Was it weird I called you sweetheart?
No! Not at all!
I'm glad you think the same way I do.
I thought to myself that I was moving too fast.
I'm going to speak comfortably now.
That resort, if there is anyone, do you want to come with me?
My company is honored to do business with the best resort in Macao.
Our company is honored to do business with Chemical Inc. as well.
Thank you.
I am honoured to serve you while you are staying here.
In any case, is this the place?
Yes. When you get off the gondola and start walking this way,
An orchestra would start playing.
Then you can go over there and do the proposal that you planned.
Over there?
Why didn't the person who is going to become your wife come here with you?
She had something important to do so she is coming here in the afternoon.
Before that, I wanted to check.
Of course.
Our enemy, Lee Gun.
Whatever we have to do... that evil human being,
We have to drop him into the trap.
Ji Yeon, I have arrived!
Unnie, you are finally in Macau!
You have to enjoy it until you book your next flight.
You just let it go today.
But, what should I do tonight?
It hasn't been long since we have started dating. I'm worried...
Why are you worrying?
You went with the man that you like.
You like him, isn't it obvious you also go?
It isn't perhaps your first time, right?
Ah, Lawyer Min is coming. I'm going to leave now.
It was crowded at the currency exchange booth.
This must have been heavy!
Why didn't you tell me to carry it?
It feels like I forced you to.
It's not like that!
Macau is really awesome!
- Let's go!
- Alright!
Yes, I just arrived.
I said that I know! I also put my life on the line.
Hey!
Hey! I said I'm not joking!
We have really put our lives on the line!
I'm requesting this of you, okay?
Ah, this lady. Just watch what happens if you don't put your life on the line.
You know how much money I've invested in her?
President, I don't think you have to worry about it.
Miss Kim is a pro in this area.
Let's get to work.
Carefully, carefully...
Hey, be careful!
Now no matter what, we have to feed it to that monkey.
That's right!
If he eats this, he is going to be strong tonight.
- We have to be successful. Are you sure about this?
- Of course!
Hey!
What are you two doing here?
What's going on?
He seems to be asking something.
Asking?
Of course I know. Ha mu, Ha mu.
Ha mu, Ha mu
What language are you speaking in? Do they have an accent...
Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry! Hurry up!
There are so many things to do! Hurry! Hurry!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
There are so many things to move! Get it together!
No!
What are we going to do?
You are like that.
You don't understand men's pride.
And even when I said that we can pay half each, you kept arguing that you wanted to pay for everything.
This is my ticket, so I should be the one paying.
Half and half is a little...
It's not like it's half chicken with sauce and half fried chicken.
I understand. But tonight, I will take care you.
Oh my...
Don't be shy. Think about it.
We are almost there.
Oh, it's here, honey.
- Come in.
- Okay.
It isn't famous for nothing. It is pretty great.
Pretty!
Wow, this is great.
What should we do now?
Huh?
What does he mean by that?
Perhaps, right after we're here?
Do you have somewhere you want to go?
Oh, I saw the brochure,
There are swimming pool, spa, and casino.
Casino...
Then where should we go first?
Then I am going to take a look, so rest.
Okay.
My honey, you must be tired.
Lawyer Min must be shy when we are alone.
Wow, what am I going to do with the back? It is downright lethal.
Hi!
Your back is pretty lethal too.
You are Korean?
I am Miss Kim, who will burn down Seoul and will eventually take over this Macau.
I'm lawyer, Min Bun Chon.
Casino and a beauty is two things that cannot be seperated.
Where did Lawyer Min go?
I shouldn't catch a cold.
The air condition is at high.
He said that he is just going to take a look...
Did something happen?
This is the real beginning.
Se Ra...
Thank you.
For coming back to Korea,
and coming to travel with me.
I know that you coming back to Korea
Is not just happy for you.
And I, who is proposing to you,
May seem selfish to you.
But... I...
Instead of being next to you when you are proud
And is at the top of her life,
I want to be next to you during a difficult time,
Who can share that burden with you.
Even if you like it when I'm smiling,
But I want to be someone that you want to see when you cry.
Can I do that?
I love you, Se Ra.
Will you marry me?
What was that sound?
Who are you?
There is someone, right?
Excuse me!
Is someone here? There is someone, right?
It seems like someone is here. I know.
Cool, cool!
The effects are showing!
What are you, are you a gold digger?
- Gold digger?
- How do you expect me to believe this kind of unbelievable situation?
What the!
We just came here to have fun anyways.
Let's just think that our partners changed.
Have confidence.
From now on, you are a queen.