Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Fated Team @ Viki
What is this sound?
The door is locked! Why is the door locked?
Are we prisoners or something?
Open the door!
Ahjumma, just hit me instead like earlier. Huh?
Episode 4
Excuse me. I'm sorry,
for many reasons. You even got hit because of me.
Your mom is severely wild.
Different than her daughter.
At least she gave us blankets.
So? Are you really going to sleep here?
We have no choice.
No matter what we say, my mom will never open the door for us.
Chief Tak! Chief Tak!
There's a door there!
It's locked...
Locked... That one might be open.
Careful, careful.
Can you get out from there?
Then should I dig a tunnel with a spoon?
I should! Just go over there, you're disrupting me.-Yes.
But you should be careful.
This is ridiculous. Really!
Why... didn't you tell me?
About the baby...
You had the chance to tell me.
Sorry. I wanted to tell you, but
I couldn't bring myself to say it.
Um. You're hungry, right?
This is a "seaweed ear," would you like some?(part of the seaweed at the root that's not common)
"A seaweed ear?" Why is there an ear on seaweed?
You haven't had anything to eat yet.
Usually people get angrier when they're hungry.
Just a little to get rid of your hunger for now...
Forget it, forget it. How can I eat that?
Well, even so... I can't ignore your sincerity...
Give me a little.
What kind of taste is this?
Anyway, in this country village there isn't any...
How is it? It's edible, isn't it?
Do you think I'm eating it because it's good?
I'm forcibly eating it to survive.
Give me some more.
I have to live a long, long life.
Surprisingly, you're not a picky eater.
I thought you'd be picky about everything since you're from a wealthy family.
I know, right. It's not like I'm Tarzan of the jungle.
In this sort of place.
Eating this sort of stuff.
I have to live a long life. Ugh, it tastes so bad.
Would you like to try this, too?
Why? What is it this time?
Is it a cochlea?
What is this?
Isn't that a fish eyeball?!
It's really chewy.
Should I pull out the other side?
Our CEO
hates skipping meals the most.
So I can drop off food, (something done in prison)
at least make some rice balls.
He won't die from skipping one meal.
Also, the storage room is full of food.
Then,
lock me in with him.
Why do you want to go in?
Perhaps, do you like our Mi Young?
Ah, I'd rather prefer the oldest sister...
Oh my... me?
That, that... it's not like that.
Aigoo, you frustrating fellow.
We have to lock them up together so they can either become attached or detached,
a decision will be made.
Looking at him from before,
I don't think he hates her.
Ah, really. This.
Do you think anyone would like this?
You probably couldn't even give it to someone.
What is this?
Wish Box? What's a Wish Box?
Oh!
No, give it! -Wait, wait. Let me read it.
It must be something amazing.
No, you can't!
Why?
It won't be interesting.
If it's really not interesting, I'll give it back.
He really can't see it...
Let me read it to see how amazing it is.
I hope my friend can
return the stuff she borrowed.
Why can't you ask your friend to give back the things she borrowed?
Does your friend have something on you?
I feel bad.
Maybe she couldn't give it back because she lost it.
I shouldn't put her in a difficult situation.
And what's this?
If I do an errand, I wish my friends would
tell me "thank you," even just once.
Did you have some sort of trauma when you were little?
This is a serious disease, a disease.
Stop reading them.
I told you they were boring.
One more. Last, last. Last.
I hope Dad
went somewhere nice in Heaven.
When did your father pass away?
He used to go out on boats.
He passed away when I was young.
I missed him so I put this in the Wish Box.
You're similar to me.
When I was young, my father
and mother also passed away from a car accident.
Don't worry too much.
I thought about it and
I think it's only right that I go to the hospital tomorrow.
Ah, um... -You already have a girlfriend that you want to marry.
Realistically, we won't be able to raise this child.
Even if I raise him on my own,
even after you two are married,
you will still be concerned.
This baby will become
a burden to you and your wife.
I don't want to give the baby
a life without blessing.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Kim Mi Young... I'm sorry.
No, it's alright.
It's my mistake for going to the wrong room.
Tomorrow, let's go to the hospital together.
I won't be able to take responsibility,
but I still don't want to let a girl go through something so hard alone.
I can go alone.
Wait a moment.
Lie here.
Yes.-Lie down.
Put this on.
I'm ok...
And... don't refuse, because I'm going to go to the hospital with you.
I'm not going to let you go by yourself.
Lie down now.
Good night. -Good night.
Still, I think it is really fascinating that
we've met 4 times, and we've slept together 2 of the times.
That connection between people is really
hard to understand.
If we met in a good situation,
I guess we would call it
destiny.
♫ Even a bad fate may turn to love. ♫
♫ Shout and call out.♫
♫ I only love you.♫
♫ My heart wants you, you who is like fate. ♫
♫ I love you. ♫
Mosquitoes!
I'm going to kill all of you! All the mosquitoes!
Kim Mi Young!
I'm going to the hospital.
You don't have to worry.
I will cheer up.
Kim Mi Young!
I was going to wake you up just now.
Where... where is the hospital?
Obstetrics, obstetrics!
What about obstetrics?
What is this?
That girl! These two were playing with fire.
And now she is going to get an abortion!
Nothing will happen if we go after her right now.
I'm going to break her legs if something were to happen.
So where is this? Quickly! Where?
But I think the first ship has already left. What are we going to do?
What do you mean? We have to make a ship.
We have to make one!
Follow me.
Wake up now!
Why? Why?
What is this? There is nothing here.
Is she answering the call or not?
Why, why, why?
Mi Young isn't picking up.
She must be causing trouble for real.
That girl, seriously...
Are we really going to have to make a ship?
Ship, ship, ship, ship!
Here, here!
Hello? Isn't that President Choi?
We are coming, we are coming.
Nothing is working without me.
I'm coming, coming, just wait a bit.
Hurry up!
Obstetrics
Okay,
I made the right decision.
Is it done yet? How much longer do I have to wait?
I told you, wait a little longer.
We are on a rotation right now.
Ok. Give me a notice when it is finished.
Hello,
I came for a surgery.
I can't hear you. What did you come here for again?
That, that, that surgery.
Oh, you are
the person from the church.
Don't you remember?
Oh, Priest.
Hello.
Wait.
From now on, how are we going to find her?
You said that there are three hospitals here in total, right?
One on the three way road, one next to the market, and one downtown.
We need to break into groups to find her.
Me and Chief Secretary Tak.
Mi Young's mother with the sisters.
Okay, okay.
And you two, since you guys are always scheming things together.
Hamo-hamo~~
We will go from the farthest.
If someone finds her, call everyone, ok?
Let's hurry up!
Hurry and find her.
I'm sorry.
Every time I see you, I tell you horrible things.
There is nothing to be sorry about.
The only thing I did was listen to you.
You are the one who is going through a hard time.
But how come you are here, Priest?
I heard that the person I wanted to meet is here,
but it is more nerve wracking than I thought.
I wanted to look good.
You look nice even now.
Have some confidence.
I wanted to cheer you up,
but there is nothing I can tell you except for you to rethink it.
It is something you can't have back even if you regret it later.
Priest,
I have a favor to ask you.
Can you pray with me?
Huh? Pray?
To be honest, I'm not...
Well, if I can help you with that.
I get confused sometimes.
Praying is all about the heart, so...
Now, you just need to talk comfortably, like you talked to me before.
Kim Mi Young! Kim Mi Young!
Kim Mi Young!
Please take pity on
the baby that met a
very, very bad mother.
Kim Mi Young!
Please let it go to a wonderful place.
For not being able to protect this baby,
I'm very, very sorry..
I'm sorry. Amen.
Thank you for helping.
I'm relieved that I could help.
I'll see you later.
Yes.
Priest,
don't be nervous and strengthen up.
Strength!
♫ When I open my eyes ♫
♫ let me hear it. ♫
♫ the words of "I love you", my melody. ♫
CEO! CEO!
CEO!
Kim Mi Young!
Kim Mi Young. Kim Mi Young.
Excuse me. I'm looking for a patient named Kim Mi Young. She has big eyes and pale skin.
One moment please.
Why are you looking for her so hard?
You are going to have the baby?
At any rate, a girl shouldn't come to a place like this alone.
Are you okay? It hurt a lot, didn't it?
You jerk!
I'm really sorry. I was wrong.
I'm really sorry, okay?  -You're really sorry? We're really over.
Yes, I've found her. Kim Mi Young is in consultation right now.
You just have to relax. I will take care of everything.
Here. Right here.
Right... here.
You won't be able to see it well because it's still early.
Here, this is the baby right here.
Looking at it right now, the baby is about 0.2 cm.
0.2...
0.2 cm?
It's much smaller than you thought.
But the fetus can understand everything the parents say.
Who's there? Who are you?
I am...
The baby's father.
Ah, yes.
But what is this sound?
The baby's heartbeat.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Fated Team @ Viki
According to the Mother and Child's Health Act, Article 14,
you and the baby's father are allowing me to conduct an induced abortion operation,
as you were impregnated while you were unconscious due to alcohol or sleeping medication.
Is this correct?
Yes.
Do you agree?
This is a consent form for the surgery. You just have to sign it.
This is...
But this is a life form of its own.This child will become
a burden to you and your future wife.
He's got fingers and toes. He's got everything.To the baby,
I don't want to give him a life without blessings.
Oh, peekaboo. Peakboo...
Why are you giving this to me?
What... Where...
Where are you going?!
Don't worry and relax. I'm going to put you under general anesthesia now.
Wait! Don't! Kim Mi Young, get up!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. Hurry and take this out.
Take it out.
I'm sorry.
After hearing the heartbeat, 9 out of 10 can't go through with the surgery.
What are you planning to do now?
I don't know.
But I don't think this is right.
But what are we going to do?
Mi Young is over there!
Sister-in-law!
You! Do you know what you've done?
Ah wait. Let's talk about this. Do you know how tough it was for her?
Is this something we can solve by talking? What happened? What about the baby?
The baby...
You! How could you not even stop her? Do you still call yourself a man?
Ah really!- Oh, it's the Chairwoman's car!
Oh, it's the Chairwoman's car!- What?
What is this?! What are you?!
Do you know how cruel you are! You murderer!
Listen to me, first!
This grandma of yours... My neck.
Grandma!
Ah, listen to me first, please! Everyone, just listen.
Grandma! Mi Young's mother! -What?
The baby... The baby!
Is fine. It's fine!
The baby is alright.- Is that right?
Also, Kim Mi Young,
I have made a selfish decision. I hope you will agree to it.
Yes?
I will..
I will...
What? "I will," what? Tell us what you are thinking comfortably as if you are at home. "I will," what? What?
We will have this baby.
Chairwoman, Chairwoman.
Aigoo.
That means, you will marry our Mi Young?
No, that..!
Why does it become that?
I meant that I will have the baby.
I didn't say anything regarding Kim Mi Young.
Also, I can't marry her.
What? You won't marry her but you want the baby?
Do you see our Mi Young as nothing but a surrogate mother?
No, your words are rather harsh. What I mean is...
After she gives birth to the baby, I will guarantee a new start to her life with exceptional treatment.
Chief Tak. Ah, ow, ow.
Aigoo, what a shameless punk. You want her to be a surrogate...
Hey! Who do you think we are?
Aiyoo. We don't think of you that way.
In my eyes, you're our in-laws and Mi Young is my granddaughter-in-law,
And I see the baby as my great-grandchild.
I've decided. I will definitely get them married.
Tell me what you think. I heard the blabber that he said, but
you must have something in mind, too.
For me, I think it's practically impossible for us to get married.
What..? Are you in your right mind?
We conceived this baby by mistake, not out of love.
Marriage should happen out of love.
That is exactly what I'm trying to say!
That's what I mean!
Shut up! How dare you..
It's alright.
There's nothing more to say here, especially when the person involved is coming out like this.
End of discussion. Take your irresponsible grandson and leave from here.
I will deal with my own daughter.
Aigoo, aigoo, you can't.
Mi Young is now my granddaughter-in-law, too.
Hold on! Sister-in law...
just say you'll get married.
CEO, Chairwoman...
Why doesn't my sister-in-law marry your grandson, and we'll become in-laws afterward!
So, why don't you cut our factory some slack?
We'll starve to death without the soap factory.
Mi Young, please save us.
Mi Young, we beg of you. You just need to make up your mind.
Enough! What kind of embarrassment is this?!
Although we sold our factory and land, we have never sold our souls before!
I won't stand still if you try to cling onto them one more time!
President Park, you have a boat at least, so you have something to lean on!
But we have nothing if we lose the factory!
Mi Young, please think this through.
Our lives are in your hands.
I told you to stop!  Are you not listening to me, now that the factory is bankrupt?! Is that it?!
Why are you like this so suddenly, President?
We should at least hold on to our pride to live!
STOP!
What are you guys doing with my daughter?!
She, as you can see, is not pretty nor does she have a great body.
Then, was she smart?
No, she did poorly in school as well!
Mom, why are you saying such things?
She was always last in math, too.
Even though she's lacking in so much,
instead she is also a child that can never be calculative in her head.
Even though her room is a mess because she can't throw things away (sentimental),
instead she can't also ever throw away (ignore) a person's feelings!
Even though she doesn't listen to her mother when I tell her countless times to please live more shrewdly,
she's a child that can never refuse the request of a complete stranger!
But...to our Mi Young, who is like this,
how dare you pressure her like this?!
Who are you all?
Who are you to tell her what to do?
How dare you ask this so easily?!
Marriage is like an eternal promise.
We don't know each other well enough to make such a commitment.
Even if we say that we can have the baby, marriage is a different thing.
Look at you with your senseless talk. Your stomach is so full it's about to burst!
Do you understand what you're saying?
One! You are going to have this baby and give it up to them.
Then you'll become a woman that has a past.
Two! You are going to have this baby and raise him/her yourself.
All you are going to be is a single mom. -That's right.
You still don't want to get married?
That's true but how bewildered must that other person be?
I don't think it's right to force him like this.
You... you, I want to ask you something.
Are you certain
that he pulled you out of the operating room?
Yes.
At least, he has some conscience.
Think through this carefully. It's not like there is no father.
The baby's dad is alive and well. Why in the world would you have this baby as a single mom?
This is your own selfishness. Isn't that right?
Kim Mi Young,
come see me for a moment.
Okay.
He's a man. I bet he'll be amazing as a husband if they get married.
Do you have no intentions of marrying me at all?
You are a great person, Gun,
and I believe you'd be a great dad to the baby.
But you have someone you love.
I know how much you love that person.
I don't want to go through with this marriage if it's going to make someone unhappy.
I've already lost
my qualification as a man to Se Ra.
And although it was our mistake,
the fact that the baby in your stomach is our child
will not ever change.
I'm already the bad guy,
but...
I want to be a great dad to the baby.
You mean...
Of course, Se Ra is still the only one for me right now,
and I can't guarantee how much
and when my heart will move towards you,
but I will promise you this one thing.
At least to our baby,
I want to be a great dad.
If you can accept this,
yes,
let's get married.
I, too,
want to be a great mom to this baby.
Yeah.
Help out over here, please!
Hello!   Are you okay?
Honey! You look so handsome!  Come over here!
I've always looked like a celebrity.
Please clear this over here!
Mi Sook! You're here! Today you went for a red fashion.
With the elders of both families...
I wonder if she's done getting ready.
Are you ready?
Here.
What is this?
Mom, getting married today is a little too fast, don't you think?
Then do you want to wait until your belly is as big as a mountain to go then?
I know buying things together as newlyweds and going on a honeymoon is part of the fun in getting married,
but what can you do? What's done is already done.
They can have the baby, we can reserve a banquet hall
and have a stunning wedding one more time!
I felt bad that I wasn't able to prepare a dowry because it was so last minute.
Then why don't we prepare everything then, too?
What dowry?
The best dowry has already been prepared right here.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Fated Team @ Viki
My Gun.
Hello?
Hello? Gun?
Are you really Gun? It's you, right?
It's me.
Hold on. Don't hang up, you can't hang up, okay?
Se Ra! Where are you going? We're going to start soon!
Se Ra..
Gun!
I actually have something to say to you..
Do you know how long I've been waiting for you to call?
You wouldn't know.
I didn't know how painful it was to wait like this.
I..
I've wronged you greatly.
Of course you've wronged me.
To be honest, as a human being you've made me wait too long.
Although you had every right to be upset.
But don't do this again, okay?
And about the proposal turning out like that...
I'm sorry once again.
Don't be sorry.
I'm even more sorry.
Then we're calling it even, okay?
We're letting this go completely, okay?
There's no one but you.
You called exactly at the right time.
Se Ra, hurry.
It seems like someone's looking for you. Is something going on today?
Today's my first performance as the prima ballerina.
The first day I stand on stage.
Oh, I see.
To be honest, I was a bit worried I might mess up because I was so nervous.
But now that I've heard your voice, I think I can do well.
Se Ra...
Do well today.
Se Ra, there's no time. Everyone's waiting.
Gun, thank you for calling me.
I love you. I'll call you.
Se...
Se Ra..
Here comes the groom!
Applause!
He's handsome!
Brother-in-law! You look so handsome!
Brother-in-law!
He's really handsome.
Here comes the bride!
Pretty! Wow! She's so pretty!
She's beautiful.
She's a goddess!
Cute! You're really pretty.
Beautiful!
Now, the bride and groom will exchange their vows.
Do you the bride, Kim Mi Young,
promise to take Lee Gun as your lawfully wedded husband,
through happiness, sickness, and loneliness,
and to love him unconditionally
without change?
Yes.
Do you, husband, Lee Gun, promise this as well?
Come now, come now...
Your voice is too soft!
YES!!!!!
He's answered 'Yes', everyone you've heard his answer!
Congratulations!
Now, there will be the exchange of the rings.
This is what your father wore.
♬ I had no idea you'd be my life.♬
♬ For when I looked into your eyes, I knew someday you'd be my wife.♬
♬ I know there's times when I am wrong.♬
Applause!
Ring!  - I did well, right?
This is a proposal ring!
It can't be worn by another woman first! It'll bring bad luck!
♬ You took my heart so unexpectedly.♬
Applause! ♬ I knew that you would be the one.♬
♬ I always knew that there was something special about you♬
♬ the day that you walked into my life.♬
Why don't you stay here for a couple of nights?
I will take care of all the company matters.
No, no. Take him with you.
It's not like he runs a small corner store. He's in charge of a huge enterprise.
I understand that much. It was an unexpected marriage, after all.
Son-in-law Lee,
you know what'll happen if you wrong our Mi Young, right?
It won't be the rice scoop, but a baseball bat that'll fly your way.
Okay, okay.
Then my granddaughter-in-law, you stay here with your mom for a couple of days before you come.
Your mom must be sad to send off her youngest daughter.
I will prepare a beautiful newlywed's room in the meantime.
That's alright, right?
Yes, then I will do that.
Okay~
Then..
Yes, yes. Have a safe trip back.
I'm leaving.
You go ahead.
CEO!!!
Oh my.
Aigoo, aigoo...
I'm out of breath.
CEO, I'm really thankful that you have accepted all the factory workers,
so I prepared this amazing gift for you.
I heard the men in your family
are lacking a bit in stamina. So, that's why you're the 9th generation of the only sons.
What kind of nonsense are you spouting?! Our family is not just normal.
We're above normal!
Then from now on, you will be above normal and become the greatest in Korea!
As long as you have this!
What is this?
Open it when you get to Seoul.
I wasn't going to brag or anything,
but I'm the best contributor to this wedding, aren't I?
This is our island's finest selection at the same level as our famous soap.
We have developed this ourselves.
That's right. This is what brought
you and our sister-in-law together.  - Hush.
Don't say anymore. Hurry and get on the boat!
The chairwoman is waiting.
Where is Chief Secretary Tak? Not taking care of his CEO...
It's strange.
I never knew the sea that you look upon from a dock would look so sad.
Everything with the word "Jang" added to it is sad.
Station (like a bus station), airport, dock,
and Chief Secretary Tak.
Mi Sook, I don't know when it'll be,
but be well until we meet again.
You too, Chief Secretary.
Mi Sook!
Chief Secretary Tak!
Yes, Chief Secretary, yes! (I hear you calling my name)
Let's go.
What is this?
Just hold it. She wants us to say our goodbyes.
Okay.
Bye!
Have a safe trip!
Be well, Mi Sook!
Brother-in-law! Have a safe trip!
Very good!
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Fated Team @ Viki
Kim Hee Won
I heard your name was Kim Mi Young when you were little.
Yes, I remember that clearly.
My older brother used to call out, "Mi Young, Mi Young."
Do you, by any chance,
remember this photo? It was at the zoo.
I can't tell from this picture.
I have a memory of going to the zoo with my older brother.
I heard you have a scar from a fire, is it ok for me to see it?
Do you know how you got the scar?
Of course, I think it was when I was 10.
The kettle on the heater in the orphanage fell.
My sister got the scar when she was 4.
I wish you were my brother.
Oppa...- Are you okay?
How is our baby?
I'm really sorry.
For not being able to protect this baby,
I'm really, really sorry.
I'm sorry.
Star, I can see a star, Chief Secretary Tak.
Your wife is looking at you from there.
Madam, hello.
Hello.- Hello.
CEO,
because it wasn't Miss Se Ra but Mi Young,
I was surprised.
But I'm glad that the CEO who is 9th generation's only son,
got not only a wife, but a child, like a 1+1 deal.
It makes me very happy.
Everyone is so happy.
My grandma is happy, and Mi Young's mother is happy.
Chief Secretary Tak is happy, too.
But I...
I... I can only laugh.
Only laughter...
Hey, but... (suddenly speaking in lower terms)
It's not "hey".
I'm sorry. But what about Mrs. Mi Young attracted you?
She is very different from Miss Se Ra.
You really like a wide variety of girls.
Chief Secretary Tak, what do you mean by attracted?
Attracted?
It was a mistake.
Aren't you going to open this?
President Park told you to open it when you get to Seoul.
Chief Secretary Tak can have it. I hate him so much that I can't stand a word he says.
What is this?
Strength, strength "Joagra".
Really.
Even with one gulp you will become
the Superman of the night. - Superman!
You can go around Hong Kong 3 times in one night and 24 hours isn't enough.
A super stimulant for
those who are afraid of the night. It says it is a stimulant.
Stimulant?
This is our Island's specialty.
We, two, invented it ourselves!
You, and my sister-in-law...
Don't say it.
Drink, Drink!- Health tonic, health tonic.
It stimulates me?
Oh, good. Cool~ Cool~
Then...
I'm sorry, I fell asleep.
I didn't notice that you came in.
So, it was because, because, of this?
Then, because of those islanders, I..
I got in this mess? - CEO, what do we do?
Then, this, this, this...
I fell in their trap, then?!
Does it even make sense?
Act all innocent in the front,
and in the back, cheat like this?
How?!
I cannot forgive this.
I'm never going to forgive this.
Chief Secretary Tak!
Oh!
Why are you here?
What do you mean? I came here to escort you.Give it to me.
No, it's ok. I'll do it.
It is not fine with me.
From now on, you have to be used to this.
Let's go.
Yes.
Is the restaurant doing fine?
- Yes, of course.- And is Miss Mi Sook doing well, too?
- Ah, yes.- Get in, please.
Get in, get in,
Thank you.
Huh!
The CEO is really busy today, so he couldn't come. Continue on getting in the car.
Yes.
I thought it was all my responsibility.
"It happened because of my mistake. That's right."
"I should take responsibility."
But now,
I feel like I've been unfairly cheated.
If it wasn't for that medicine, if only not for that woman,
maybe she might be part of the plan...
They must be on the same team, same team.
Same team, same team.- You want to vent your anger on anyone
and you feel like you will explode right away if anyone touches you, right?
You can't get to sleep?
Yes. If I drink like a mad man
and I work out 'till I feel like dying,
I sleep like a dead man, but after exactly 30 minutes,
my eyes open and
my heart...
hurts so much and the first thing that comes to my mind is
"I got married!"
"I got married"...
I got married.
I got married!!!!!
But the thing that makes me so mad is
the fact that,
I need to live my married life
with that snail woman.
What do you mean by "snail"?
You mean the Mud Snail Bride (from Korean folk tale)?
No, no, no not something good like that.
It is about a terrifying snail that lives in Yeoul Island.
Terrifying snail.
You are scared of snails? Why?
The thing about snails is that
they look innocent from the outside,
but their suction force is so strong. It's just incredible!
If you get sucked by a snail,
that terrifying sucking feet,
slowly, little-by-little, piece-by-piece,
with a giant house on its back,
toward the target,
slowly, little-by-little, piece-by-piece, getting closer..
These... - Hello.
These are worse then turtles.
But at the end, they acquire it, the victory.
They win.
But at some point,
when I think about that scary snail that will be on top of my head...
I... I... I can't do anything but laugh.
Fated to Love You~Preview~
Finally, a piece of luck has entered our family.
Do you think that you fit in with this place?
Damn it!
Wait, what are you doing?
Although she is armed with a countrified and naive look,
she might be a Master of Lies.