Subtitles brought to you by The Fated Team @ Viki
Se Ra,
I love you Se Ra.
Will you marry me?
What's that sound?
Anyone here?
Someone is here, right?
Right?
Is someone here? There is someone here, right?
I think there is someone here. I know everything... I do, I do.
Am I hearing things because I'm nervous?
Hahaha
Miss, fashion, your airport fashion.
your sunglasses are awesome.
Ow, you are really late.
I'm ready to depart.
Yeah. I took care of the matter well.
How about you? Are you done with work?
That's good.
Let's eat a lot of yummy food and lazily roll around in bed all day long.
Ok. I'll be there soon.
Ok. I love you
Miss Se Ra, when you arrive at Macau, please listen to our president.
President is planning a pro..
He will be waiting in a professional way.
ok. I will.
Come after you answer the phone call.
Hello?
Oh, Thomas
Yeah. I'm in Korea
Of Course, I was a little upset.
What?
We changed our minds, Se Ra
We want you to be our prima ballerina as Odette
Please hurry up and come back to New York as soon as possible.
I just thought of the first time we met.
When was that? That was 6 years ago. We were so young.
We've been going out for so long.
You just realized that?
Look at all these wrinkles I got from waiting for you for so long. I can't even laugh.
See? See?
I'm not going to let my love leave me. Ever again.
Your shoulder and back is so tense.
You must have had lots of worries.
Please do a good job.
I have an important event coming up.
Important event coming up.
We failed in our first try,
but we will succeed in the second try.
It hurts! Do it gently.
Ha mu ha mu
Hurry up
Hurry, hurry
woh woh woh
I'm telling you, I have an important event coming up.
You can stop now. Stop. Stop
Stop. Ahhhhh
Good work, good work.
Drink?
natural...natural...
Thank you.
Drink up drink up
It's going in, it's going in
Good~
Cool! Cool! Cool~
It's awesome!
Great! Great~
You!
Chinese. Chinese. I have a mole. a mole.
It's an illusion. Illusion.
Wait a minute.
What is this?
Aren't you President Park?
This is President Park!
Why are you here?
Why did you come here?
It's fine that you brought the factory, but why did you fire the workers?
Majority of the people in our Yeo Wool Island work at that soap factory
Are you trying to starve all the Islanders?
Please help us Islanders.
Please help.
Hey, why would I give you the factory I brought legally?
Don't just sit here, go back to your island and get the people out of the factory!
I'll go there in 2 weeks and close that factory.
President, president, president,
Please, president, please
Let go! Let go!
Even if you keep on begging like this,
I'm not going to listen to you.
Not going to listen to you! Get out!
President... Go! No, president...
President!!!
Wow, he fell,
The medicine must be working gradually.
The stimulant from our island is the best, you know.
oh. There he goes again..
Aww
It's time to go to Se Ra.
Lets focus!
Oh. wow..
He won't even notice if anyone were to kidnap him.
I put double the amount of the stimulant in the drink.
Hey, let's start our work.
Should we?
Ding hao.
ding hao (not korean)
Oh my..
Oh my.. Look, look look here
It is very present.
This is really
Great
Oh, he scared me
Let go, go, go
Hey, push, push, push
Push it that way
That way? Oh, that way
Dude, that way
No, that way
It's too hard.
It's there
Slide the key
2006, 2008, and 2009
What is this?
What is this? It's both 2006.
Father,
Husband,
Son,
This time, our 9th generation's only son, Gun.
need to succeed in his proposal. Please look after him.
So that he leaves with 2, comes back with 3.
Please give him a hand.
Father, forgive me for
not using the honorifics
(It's a song about making rice cake)
Last night, what, what
I really did it?
Oh. what am I going to do?
What do I do now?
Let's stay like this for a little bit more.
Maybe it's because it's morning, but his voice sounds a bit different.
Lawyer Min must have worked out a lot
I knew he had a warm heart,
but I didn't know he had fit chest
I'm sorry.
I fell a sleep.
I didn't even realize when you came in.
I'm sorry.
No, it's ok. I'm sorry I came late.
When did you come?
We came together.
We came together?
Who are you?! Ah!!
Who are you? Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Great! What?!
What are you?
Our Island's worst enemy President Lee Gun,
You started the fight,
so don't blame us
Were you surprised?
I'll introduce properly,
this is our Island's prettiest girl
Miss Kim!
What? Mi Young
Why are you here?
This is my sister-in-law
Wait, wait, stay there
Stay right there.
Stop right there!
Stop, stop right there
I'm going to do something about this.
Open the door! Just open the door!
What did you just do here? Who are you?
Then why are you in my room?
What are you saying? Your room?
Seriously, just come out and let's talk.
Manager, manager.
Hurry up and come. I'm not sure if she is a robber or a pervert
but there is a weird girl here.
My girl friend is gone!
This is the worst, so call the police
Hurry up and call the police. You need to hurry.
Stop right there.
Open the door. Seriously, who are you?
Se Ra, what did you do to my Se Ra?
I don't know what Se Ra is.
I don't know what just happened either.
What is this situation? I'm going crazy.
Where are you Lawyer Min?
Open the door. Open the door and tell me!
Ok.
I'll get out.
Oh! Wait!
I caught you! You pervert.
Wait a minute, your face looks familiar.
Ring!
Him?
What are you doing here..
So you approached me on purpose from that time on?
Is that why you tried so hard to find my ring for me?
What are you talking about?
I felt sorry that you fell because of me.
Tell me the truth.
Who are you?
You're a female con, aren't you?
A female con?
I am not.
I have nothing to do with that. I am just a normal person.
Normal? Yeah right.
How can a normal lady come into a strange man's room..
Why did you come here?
I'm not a female con!
Do you normally not trust what people say?
You have to say something trustworthy to trust you!
Wait a minute
Wait a minute, then I spent the night here with a woman like you?
What have I done with a woman like you here?
Hello?
I'm dumbfounded too here.
What did you do?
I'm going crazy.
You think I wouldn't know that you and your brother-in-law planned this?
How many times must I tell you that's not true?
I have no idea what's going on as you.
If you did anything to my Se Ra,
then I'm going to kill you!
Number 7!
Stop. Action.
Stop!
That's them. Hurry and go find them.
Aigoo that was surprising.
That was Mi Young, right?
Right.
I didn't see wrong, right?
But what is your sister-in-law doing over there?
This stupid girl..
A message came.
Room 2009 is missing?
What does that mean?
How could a room just disappear?
How should I know?
Over there!
Run!
Let go!
Arirang~ Arirang~
Camera!
Get them!
Hurry!
I am looking into it, but it's been so long it's not as easy.
And we're not supposed to tell about adoption.
So it's hard to keep track of.
I'm sorry for asking such difficult favor.
No need to be sorry.
If it's your business Daniel, of course I will help.
Thanks to you our orphanage runs very well.
It's nothing.
Mr.! Pass the ball please.
Pass us the ball!
If you find anything, then give me a call.
I will come by often.
Okay.
Mister?
Come here!
Boss, Se Ra is
confirmed to be in air to New York.
I should've sat down next to her on her flight.
Thought she'd come back right out after checking in.
Boss. I am so sorry.
Alright. I got you.
New message
Gun,
First of all, I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
This trip's purpose and all,
I had a sense of what it meant.
And when that moment comes,
I felt my heart pounding just thinking about it.
But I am still returning to America.
My heart hurts from thinking how much you will be disappointed, Gun.
But Gun,
I tried not to, but after not getting the role from audition,
My feelings were hurt as I went to Korea.
That's how I honestly felt.
Please let me do ballet just once more.
I don't want to marry with this feeling of defeat and failure.
After I
I will return to you, Gun.
I'm sorry.
Love you.
Hey.
How much were you told to get?
No matter how much you like money, how could you plan such thing with your family?
It's nothing like that. I told you.
I really have no idea what's going on.
It was my first time seeing my brother-in-law at that room too.
I told you not to put on any shows.
It said 2006, so I went in thinking it was my room.
You can check for sure.
But coincidentally, I was in that room?
Just like before. And this time too?
You expect me to believe in such nonsense!
I'm dumbfounded myself how something like this could happen.
Please believe me.
Okay. Let's say I believe in what you're saying.
But you're abandoned by those people.
They left you here alone and ran away to save their lives.
Whatever the reason is, the fact that you are abandoned by your family,
won't change.
There must have been a reason.
My brother-in-law and that company president are good people.
Those good people would do such crazy things?
Hey, just tell me the truth.
You came after me, didn't you?
Are you even a guest at this hotel?
Boss. It is true that this guest is reserved in room 2006.
It has been confirmed.
Still,
can't believe you until I see it with own eyes.
Then you can go see it for yourself.
Instead of just being suspicious.
Follow me.
What is this? Huh?
What is this?
And how could you open the door?
The door was open.
I inserted the car and pushed the door to open it, but it was open, I think.
You think?
Yes.
This was it?
Does this make any sense?
Everyone go back.
If there's any problem, give us a call.
We'll be on standby.
How could this make sense?
Excuse me..
I'm sorry that this happened, but
my brother-in-law and that company president,
what will happen to them?
They can't go to jail.
Could you please not send them to jail?
How could you worry about others when you are like that?
What am I doing here with a women like you?
Anyways, it's not over yet so just keep that in mind.
Does it feel good?
Lover!
I think I'm doing well. Doesn't this feel good?
There, there.
-Here?
This is where it needs to be loosened up.
Honey, you're here?
Is she that woman who you told me about that is so into you?
Her dark circles appear as if she's been having a good time with someone else.
How could you...
How could you..
Where are your shoes?
What have you been doing all night?
Come sit down.
You were surprised, weren't you?
We came here to have fun anyways.
Let's just think our partners changed.
If you look at it like that it's all in good fun.
How could you do this with another woman?
I'm sorry. Calm down.
Honey, your type really sucks.
How could you come on vacation with this kind of girl?
Give me back the earring.
It's mine.
Give that to me.
Give me that earring.
What the?
Someone would think I stole yours.
It looks cheap anyways.
Just throw that away.
You can't do this.
How could you..
Why are you crying?
Go.
Get out of here.
I reserved this room under my name.
Do you know how excited I was?
You don't know how much I liked you.
I think you've misunderstood.
You think I'm your boyfriend or something?
I was just being nice because you were innocent and cute. And now, you're all over me.
You're funny.
Don't delude yourself.
You're just a post-it girl just like your nickname.
Someone that I can make use of and when I don't need it, I can just throw away.
I'm a lawyer.
Do you think a lawyer would want to date an unemployed?
How could a nobleman go out with a peasant?
Does that make any sense?
Let's not do this, (nastily)...
Wear this.
Get up.
There is no need to talk to a thing like him.
Let's go.
Hey, what are you?
You're a nobleman?
You're just trash.
People like you aren't even considered as peasants.
Let's go.
That bastard.
Why would you listen to all that?
Are you stupid?
This is mine.
So what is this?
Is it expensive?
It's mine.
This is mine.
This is just mine.
In my life, I was never lucky with contest, but was chosen
...I'm even able to travel
Finally...
Luck comes to me too.
Just...I
I just wanted, with my whole heart, to someone
I only wanted to love someone with all my heart.
I really tried.
But...now, what am I, really..
Why are you crying?
Why are you crying!? Who are you trying to please?!
It's just coming so what am I suppose to do?!
Has you life ended?!
You can show that it hasn't and live in a cool manner!
Seriously, your taste in men...
Calling that a boyfriend!
If your eyes are bad then your brain should be good at least.
I...
really liked that person.
My nickname in the company is...
post-it.
But that guy,
he treated me differently.
I really liked him.
That's why I anticipated this vacation so much.
I prepared everything.
This makes no sense.
This makes no sense!
Why?
Why are people who hurt us so fine?
Why are people who are hurt always the ones to hurt?
Why is it driving me crazy?
Follow me.
Where?
From now on, you are no longer post-it.
You are crazy glue.
Once you are removed, the body and skin will be hurt even more.
I'll show you how great you are.
Follow me.
Omona.
What am I going to do? It is so difficult.
In her current condition, you have to pay us the double the cost.
I don't care if you want double, or triple, don't worry about the money
and transform her from head to toe.
You need to transform her to the point where people will wonder if it is even possible.
Seriously, need to change everything.
I think I look ok even now...
This is the worst part. Get rid of it first.
Use all the material you can possibly use,
and transform her as a whole
Okay, let's go.
Oh, wait..
Change everything
I think I'm ok. I did dress up today.
(oh baby, I wanna be beside you)
(like a lie, )
(I'm crying because of you)
(Oh just wanna be with you, can you hear my heart)
(My love shines through the pain)
Your eye is big
Put more eye shadow on her eye lids
It's really difficult.
You are so short, it's hard to find a dress for you.
(Love me...)
Tell me that you love me,
(The love I'm saying right now)
I have created the best work of my life.
You could say that she is a totally different woman now.
I know, right? I thought we were magicians or something.
I get it, so just show her to me.
You prepared to double the money?
Okay. Ready? Go!
Well, it's not bad.
Have confidence.
From now on, you are the queen.
No one will be able to look down on you.
Act naturally as if this is your house. Here.
Why don't you wipe the drool off your face?
What did he do to that country girl?
Call.
-Call.
Flop. (means dealing of the first three face-up cards to the board)
Raise.
-Raise.
Fourth (street)
(aka "turn" means the fourth of five cards dealt to a community card board)
River.  *means the final card dealt in a poker hand
Raise.
- Raise.
Raise. Card open
Jack, triple.
Seven pair
okay
How many is this?
Now that I found my lucky goddess, I'm on a roll.
Give me some luck.
Will it be ok?
Don't worry, just trust me.
Oh, what is that. That,
I need to resist it.
Mi Young must be suffering a lot right now.
We can't eat to save our lives...
Loyalty!
That's right.
Our sister in law...that jerk is probably giving her a hard time.
Aren't you nervous?
Yeah...
I don't think we are going to win this time. Just end it.
I can't do that as a man.
Call.
Card open.
You must be really nervous.
Whoo!
How much is this? Babe, you know it's all because of my luck right?
Of course I know, the one who told me to end it.
I'm sorry, but can I bid more?
I have too many chips.
Also, I'm kind of getting bored.
Call.
Fold, raise.
Flop
Raise
Call.
Raise.
River.
Wish me some luck.
Ok.
Here you go.
All in
Oh.. This is too much...
Full house of Ace.
There is no way I'm losing.
Even if you do that, I know it's all trickery. I can see right through you.
There are three things a gambler needs to win.
First, patience to wait for your turn.
Second, determination to follow though till the end.
Such a show off. What's the last one?
This one is,
I'll tell you after you become desperate.
Really?
Oh.. you are so scary.
But I guess I won't be hearing the third one.
Will this be enough?
All in.
Card open.
Ace. Full House.
Four of a kind of 8s.
- Won, we won!!  - Really?!?!
Omg!!
I'm so relieved!!
I was so worried that
we were going to lose due to my bad luck!
I'm so relieved.
What are you going to do?
My chips were also in there!
Hand over my money now!
What exactly are you good at?!
You weren't that great at night either..
Why are you changing your words?
You said you had a great time last night!
You said there was no other white horse like me!
White horse? Yeah right..
Don't say such nonsense!
Number 3 for a gambler is
the ability to recognize your Lady Luck.
Which is something you lacked.
No! I want a rematch.
You can't take these.
Just once. Just one more match.
You can't do this!
Yes, I can~
Don't be like this. You look low and cheap.
I thought you were from a nobility..
Why are you being like this, honey?
You shouldn't be like this to a fellow co-worker.
How are you going to see my face tomorrow at work?
Just once.. Let's just play one more time.
Look here..
It seems like this was how much you started off with.
Right here, right now, in front of this lady,
if you get on your knees and sincerely apologize,
I will return your money to you.
Here...
I'm sorry, I was wrong.
I'm really reflecting on my mistakes.
You can see it on my face, right?
I'm sorry.
Stop and stand up.
I'm so stupid, huh?
Even though you gave me a chance for revenge, I just gave up so easily.
So why do you forgive someone like that?
Because he's pitiful?
Watching him kneel in front of money
Not him, but I (looked) was pitiful.
He's a bad person, it's true.
but my feelings for him
was real.
Truth shouldn't become useless...
You and I are similar.
I as well, because Sera didn't come, became alone.
I even prepared a proposal.
Is your girlfriend's name Se Ra?
Se Ra..
I love you, Se Ra.
Will you
marry me?
If I propose, and things go wrong
it'll all be your fault!
I'm really sorry.
Because of me.. your proposal didn't work out.
I think it's like you said.. It didn't work out due to my bad luck.
No, I just said that because I was mad at the time.
It's not really your fault.
You know.. Those two men..
My brother-in-law and the CEO guy..
what they did was bad,
but it was because they were desperate,
so can you just forgive them?
Fine.
It looks like we were both victims,
since one of us asked to forgive them,
why don't we go ahead and do that.
I'll tell the security not to turn them over to the police.
Thank you.
Oh right,
my name is Gun. Lee Gun. It's a single character.
My name is very ordinary and common..
Let's hear how common it is.
- It's Kim Mi Young.
- Kim Mi Young?
What's wrong with Kim Mi Young?
There's always someone with the same name wherever I go.
There are 3 Kim Mi Youngs' at my office.
Across the nation, there are even 20,000 more.
Someone's name is "Mar" and "Kim" as their last.
So his name is "Kim Mar-ee". [seaweed rolls]
Please be confident!
Being that comman only proves
how popular the name actually is.
At first, I thought you were a weird person
but right now you're like a different person.
Ah!
Take it
Hand
It's the watch that made you Lady Luck.
We can't always win the game of life, but
But, as long as you have that "chip"
you will always have hope and the chance, so keep it well.
Thank you.
Ah!
This is my gift to you.
This is...the dog...saliva
No. I bought another one.
This is a candy that helps to fulfill love.
The words of people who succeeded with this lollipop,
I believe them.
No, I want to believe.
People who like sweet things, are people who wants to be happy.
Usually I don't believe in that...
Give it to me.
Thank you.
I'm going.
Miss Kim Mi-Young
Yesterday's event
Forget about it
Of course.
We're not going to see each other again.
And it's not good for a person to be too nice.
Be confident...and don't get intimidated.
You know it?! To be resilient.
I'll try.
I'm going to go.
♫ I'm in love with you ♫
♫ Never felt this way ♫
♫ Do you know about my love ♫
♫ You steal my heart, forever more ♫
♫ Night will come tomorrow, I will wait ♫
♫ When I open my eyes, let me hear it ♫
♫ Words of Loving me, my melody ♫
Preview
Episode 3
Miss Kim Mi-Young
I...I think I'm pregnant.
Mom
You come here... Mi-Young!
Really, it's interesting...
Someone like you, who is normal and nothing. What's there to see?
It's me, Gun
Dad.
shush. Be quiet.
Daddy!
What?